Guide to the Stanford University, Sponsored Projects Office, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-1986-200
  - Committee on Research - Meetings (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Committee on Research, (1975) (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Compliance II - Assurances Filed for Title VI, Civil Rights Ac, (1964-75) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Computing, 1971-74 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Conflict of Interest, (1974) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Conflict of Interest, (1974) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Congress - General (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Congress - Hebert Amendment, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Congress - Mansfield Amendment (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Congress - McClellan Committee Hearings, (July 1969) (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Congress - Military Recruiting, (1971-72) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Congress - Student Disruptions Legislation, (1969-1973) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Congress - Student Disruptions Legislation (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Consulting Agreements, (1966-72) (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Consulting Aud. (DCAA) Report, (3/12/76) (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Consulting Aud. (DCAA) Project Phase II, (1976) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Consulting Aud. (DCAA) - News Release (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Sponsored Projects San Joaquin Analysis. Copies of Cost Reimbursement Contract for Educational Services (Research) between The Board of Trustees of Leland Stanford Junior University and: Shell Oil, AMOCO, Getty Oil Company, Chevron USA Inc., Occidental Petroleum Corporation, Gulf Oil Corporation, Superior Oil, Texaco USA, Marathon Oil Company, Tenneco Inc., EXXON USA. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Copies of Proposal to the Petroleum Industry to Initiate the Stanford San Joaquin Basin Analysis Project (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Sponsored Projects Office Memos and Correspondence re: San Joaquin Basin Analysis (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Records, Accession ARCH-1987-130
  Accession 1987-130 contains minutes, memoranda, reports, correspondence and other records of the Committee on Research, 1970-86.
  - Committee on Research, 1970-71 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Research, 1971-72 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Research, 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Research, 1973-74 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Research, 1974-75 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Research, 1975-76 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Research, 1976-77 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Research, 1977-78 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Research, 1978-79 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Research, 1979-80 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Research, 1981-82 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Research, I, 1982-83 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Research, II, 1982-83 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Research, III, 1982-83 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Research, I, 1983-84 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Research, II, 1983-84 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Research, III, 1983-84 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Research, I, 1984-85 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Research, II, 1984-85 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Committee on Research, 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Records, Accession ARCH-1988-119
  Accession 1988-119 contains chron files from July 1, 1982 through October 31, 1983.
  - Cron file, July 1, 1982 - July 15, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cron file, July 16, 1982 - July 31, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cron file, August 1 1982 - August 15, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cron file, August 16, 1982 - August 31, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Cron file, Sep 1, 1982-Sep 15, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cron file, Sep 16, 1982-Sep 30, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cron file, October 1, 1982 - October 15, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Cron file, October 16, 1982 - October 31, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Cron file, November 1, 1982 - November 15, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Cron file, November 16, 1982 - November 30, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Cron file, December 1, 1982 - December 10, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Cron file, December 11, 1982 - December 20, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Cron file, December 21, 1982 - December 31, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Cron file, January 1, 1983 - January 10, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Cron file, January 11, 1983 - January 20, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Cron file, January 21, 1983 - January 31, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Cron file, February 1, 1983 - February 14, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Cron file, February 15, 1983 - February 28, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cron file, March 1, 1983 - March 11, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Cron file, March 14, 1983 - March 22, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Cron file, March 23, 1983 - March 31, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Cron file, April 1, 1983 - April 15, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Cron file, April 16, 1983 - April 30, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cron file, May 1, 1983 - May 15, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Cron file, May 16, 1983 - May 31, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Cron file, June 1, 1983 - June 15, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Cron file, June 16, 1983 - June 30, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Cron file, July 1, 1983 - July 15, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Cron file, July 16, 1983 - July 31, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Cron file, August 1, 1983 - August 15, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Cron file, August 16, 1983 - August 31, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Cron file, Sep 1, 1983-Sep 15, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Cron file, Sep 16, 1983-Sep 30, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Cron file, Oct 1, 1983-Oct 15, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Cron file, Oct 16, 1983-Oct 31, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Records, Accession ARCH-1990-134
  Accession 1990-134 contains assorted ERL (Electronics Research Lab) and AEL (Applied Electronics Lab) reports, a patent application of Karl R. Spangenberg, and a working notebook of A. T. Waterman, Jr.
  - Record of Invention: W. S. Perkins (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Patent Application: Spangenberg (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dissertation: "Signal Sorting in Electronic Reconnaissance" by Donald Grace (4 copies) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dissertation: "Signal Sorting in Electronic Reconnaissance" by Donald Grace (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dissertation: "Signal Sorting in Electronic Reconnaissance" by Donald Grace (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dissertation: "Signal Sorting in Electronic Reconnaissance" by Donald Grace (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ERL Report: "Design of a Folded-Line Voltage-Tuned X-Band Amplifier" (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - ERL Report: "The S-120 Rapid-Scan Radar Intercept Receiver" (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - AEL Report: "Countermeasures Repeaters Employing Frequency Memory" (2 copies) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ERL Report: "The S-130 Intercept Equipment" (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ERL Report: "Extended Range Passive Detection" (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - AEL Report: "Cascade Operation of Dispersive Traveling-Wave Tubes" (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - ERL Report: "Current Status of the SERL Rapid-Scan Intercept Receiver Program" (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - ERL Report: "A Preliminary Analysis of Inverse Gain Radar Jamming" (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - ERL Report: "Modulation Requirements for Backward-Wave Oscillators Used as Jamming Transmitters" (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Working Notebook: A. T. Waterman, Jr. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Records, Accession ARCH-1991-037
  Accession 1991-037 consists of several de-classified documents of O. Villard and W. Shockley.
  - Villard, O., NONR-255 (33) Ionospheric irregularities research (de-classified documents) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Shockley, W., letter to Frank A. Parker re: operations research reports on Malaya and Kenya (de-classified document), 8 August 1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Shockley, W., letter with paper "Study of Limited War from Operational Research Publications" (de-classified documents), 16 January 1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Shockley, W., working papers (de-classified), "Control of the Population and Related Man Power Statistics", "Work Sheets on Population Control", "Implication of the Statistics of Patrol and Ambush", "A Figure of Merit for Diffuse Combat", "Weapon Effectiveness", July 1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Records, Accession ARCH-1992-076
  Accession 1992-076 contains the correspondence files (chron) of E. Cilley 1972-79; records concerning indirect cost recovery, affirmative action, Committee on Government Relations, and the NIRT project; and patent and copyright files for SEL 300-399 projects.
  - Commission on Government Procurement (Reform) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Commission on Government Procurement, 1973-76 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Commission on Government Procurement, 1970-72 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Rebate Information (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Rebate Worksheets (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Transition Rebates, 1/77-8/78 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Indirect costs, Jan 1967 thru May 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Indirect costs, (1962-1966) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Indirect costs, (1961 and prior) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Legal Issues (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - NIH Manpower Safety Survey (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Medical Design Center (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Military Recruiting (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Some NIRT material (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - E. Cilley expense reports, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - E. Cilley expense reports, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - E. Cilley expense reports, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - SPO personnel, 1972-76 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - SPO personnel, 1972-76 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - E. Cilley chron files, Jan 1978-Jun 1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - E. Cilley chron files, Jan 1978-Jun 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - E. Cilley chron files, Jan 1978-Jun 1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - E. Cilley chron files, Jan 1978-Jun 1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - E. Cilley chron files, Jan 1978-Jun 1979 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Administrative Panel on External Affirmative Action, (1975) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Panel on External Affirmative Action, (1974) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Panel on External Affirmative Action, (1973) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Panel on External Affirmative Action, (1971-72) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Commission on University Budget Priorities (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Financial Reports Forecasting and Data, (1972) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory Cost Project, (1972) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Palo Alto-Stanford Exchange Program (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Personnel Development, (Prior to 1975) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Personnel and Employee Relations (PER) - general (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Personnel Inquiries (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Purchasing Relocation (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Staff Retreats (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - ARLO (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Prof. Leonard Hayflick (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Research Assistants, (1961-1964) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Research Associates, (1965-1969) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Research Associates, (1970) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Research Associates, (1971) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Research Associates, (1972) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Research Position Papers (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Budgets, (1971-73) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - B and P Capital Budget, (1974- ) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Budgets, (1973-74) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Budgets, (1974-75) (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Budget Priorities Commission (Task Force 1) (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - BAP III, (1972-73) (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - E. Cilley Chron Files, Sep 1972-Dec 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - COGR [Committee on Government Relations], (1976) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - COGR - General, (1975-76) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - COGR, (1974-75) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - COGR - General, (1973-74) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - COGR, (1971-72) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - COGR - EC, (April 1970-August 1971) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - COGR legislation Interaction Study Group, (1973-74) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - COGR Federal Management Developments Subcommittee, (1974) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - COGR Long Term Planning Group, (1975-) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - COGR Subcommittee on Patents and Copyrights, (1971) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - COGR State and Local Governments, (1973-74) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - NIRT - Technical Reports No.12 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - NIRT - Technical Reports No.13 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - NIRT - Technical Reports No.14 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - NIRT - Technical Reports No.15 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - NIRT - Technical Reports No.16 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - NIRT - Technical Reports No.17 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - NIRT - Technical Reports No.18 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - NIRT - Technical Reports No.19 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - NIRT - Technical Reports No.20 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - NIRT - Executive Summary - Program Planning Assistance (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - NIRT - Audit Report - Stanford Internal Audit, July 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - NIRT - Status Report: ERTI, 11-Dec-76 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - NIRT - Referenced/Cross Indexed Guide to Iranian Contract (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NIRT 1 Status Reports (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - NIRT 1 Other (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - NIRT 1 Contract and Exhibits (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - NIRT 1 Review Committee (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - NIRT 2 Contract Coverage with chart (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - NIRT - Publicity (Stanford connected); Iran Clippings (general) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Research Agreements (Proposal), (1969) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Research Assistants, (1965 to 1974) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Research Associates, (1974 to 1976) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Research Associates, (1973) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Research Management Improvement Project, (1972) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Research Park (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Affirmative Action, (1974) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Affirmative Action, (1973) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Affirmative Action, (1972) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Affirmative Action, (1969-70) (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Conflict of Interest, (1972) (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Conflict of Interest, (1964-71) (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Copyright Policy, (1973) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Copyright Policy, (1972) (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Notebook: Contract recap, March 1983 (Box 6)
  - Notebook: Contract recap, June 1982 (Box 6)
  - Engineering College Research Council (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Copyright Policy, (1967-71) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Government Property prior to, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Government Policy Group (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Guide (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence files re Harry C. Burbridge, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - SEL 300 Pearson, Allen, Shyam "Indium Arsenide Gunn Oscillator" patent issued (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - SEL 301 Barry, Lomcisney "Impulse noise eliminator" (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - SEL 302 New, Newcomb "Time-variable gyrator for ICs" patent issued (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - SEL 303 New, Treter, Newcom "Direct coupled variable gyrator" patent issued (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - SEL 304 Rao, Newcomb Time-Variable gyrator for ICs (without Zeners) Inactive (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - SEL 305 Anderson, Newcomb, Brady, New "Tapped Electronically-Variable Delay Line for ICs" Inactive (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - SEL 306 Anderson, New, Newcomb "Adjustable tuned coupled circuits in micro form" inactive (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - SEL 307 New, Anderson, Newcomb "Voltage-controlled oscillators and frequency modulators for ICs" inactive (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - SEL 308 Anderson, New, Newcomb "Signal Mixing Using Gyrators" inactive (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - SEL 309 Kino Beam Diode TWT (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - SEL 310 Norris, Gibbons "Signal Generators using Scanned Distributed Beam Diodes" (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - SEL 311 Norris, Gibbons "Wideband DC Amplifier with Unbalanced output of Optional Polarity" (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - SEL 312 Norris, Gibbons "Self Contained Complementary Amplifier" (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - SEL 313 Norris, Gibbons "Wideband DC Amplifier with Unbalanced Input and Balance Output" (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - SEL 314 Norris, Gibbons "High-Efficiency Harmonic Generator" (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - SEL 315 Norris, Gibbons "Technique for Reduction of space change effects in beam diodes" (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - SEL 316 Norris, Gibbons "Improved semiconductor target for electron bam ionization devices" (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - SEL 317 Norris, Gibbons "Electron beam-diode amplifier with sharp frequency cutoff" (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - SEL 318 Norris, Gibbons "Multiple input device for high-speed analog multiplication" (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - SEL 319 Barry (classified) "Reflector antenna" (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - SEL 320 Jackson "high resolution photographic holography" inactive (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - SEL 321 McMaster inactive (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - SEL 322 Mantey, Hoff "Digital filter/Oscillator block" (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - SEL 323 Hunter, Wohlfort "Rapid interleaved pulse train sorting" inactive (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - SEL 324 Winter "Time multiplexing DF Technique" (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - SEL 325 Winter "Simple delay-line frequency discriminator" (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - SEL 326 Crawford, Harp, Bruce "Technique for pulse storage and delayed recall" inactive (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - SEL 327 Brugler "FB Circuit for linear response to light" (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - SEL 328 Brugler "Phototransistor circuit for logarithmic response" (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - SEL 329 Brugler "Comparator circuit for optical contrast detection" (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - SEL 330 Pearson, Majerfeld, Allen "High speed current limiting device" (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - SEL 331 Cox "Elimination of phase errors due to antenna vibrations" patent issued, inactive (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - SEL 332 Schmid "HF inductively-coupled heater supply for CRT" inactive (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - SEL 333 Crawford "Imporved process for carbon deposition" inactive (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - SEL 334 Tammaru "Method for testing arrays of combinational logic" inactive (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - SEL 335 Ingalls "Bit rate integrator" inactive (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - SEL 336 Harp "Waveguide with uniform electric field strength" abandoned (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - SEL 337 Jenny "Adaptive sampling system for data compression" inactive (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - SEL 338 Huggins "Crystal growth technique" (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - SEL 339 Compton, Vincent, Baganoff "Oscillating infrared energy source" (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - SEL 340 Likeness, Wilcox "Flotation technique for testing low level accelerometers" patent issued (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - SEL 341 Glushkoff "Device for tempering steel springs" abandoned (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - SEL 342 Tiller abandoned (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - SEL 343 Epstein "Communications using modulation of ionosphere polarizations" inactive (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - SEL 344 McKinley "Gyro Axis alignment using laser mass removal" inactive (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - SEL 345 Wilshaw, Watters, Tetelman "In situ toughening by shock waves" inactive (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - SEL 346 Siegman, Trembley "Fresnel drag ring-laser angular readout" inactive (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - SEL 347 Barna "Range Doppler radar using pseudorandom FM" (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - SEL 348 Villard (classified) "Technique for reducing radar reflectivity" (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - SEL 349 Thiede "Technique for measuring R.I. variations" abandoned (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - SEL 350 Babcock "Photomultiplier tube noise reduction circuit" inactive (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - SEL 351 Cumming "Voltage or frequency memory system" inactive (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - SEL 352 Wright "Electronically tunable narrow band noise generator" inactive (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - SEL 353 McCullough "Real-time digital spectrum analyzer" (report preparation only) inactive (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - SEL 354 Lindsey "Material forming with feedback shape control" inactive (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - SEL 356 Bergstrom, Boudart "Technique for preparing highly dispersed catalysts" inactive (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - SEL 357 Kane, Scher "Satellite attitude controller" (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - SEL 358 Rehsteiner "Temperature-controlled jet deflector system" (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - SEL 359 Villard (Classified S) "Radar coding technique" (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - SEL 360 Anderson, Parlee "Nitride/liquid metal fission reactor" (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - SEL 361 Norris, Gibbons "Transfer function synthesis amplifier" (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - SEL 362 Norris, Gibbons "High performance distributed amplifier" (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - SEL 363 Norris, Gibbons "Coded pulse train generator" (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - SEL 364 Norris, Gibbons "Fast multi-position signal switch/real-time sampler" (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - SEL 365 Wright "Amplitude modulation using phased-array antennas" abandoned (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - SEL 366 Snook, Jackson "FM-CW laser system for remote measurement of smoke plume opacity" inactive (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - SEL 367 Hoff, Lund "Parallel Binary Multiplier" abandoned (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - SEL 368 Hunter "Precision time interval comparator" (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - SEL 369 Kincheloe "High capacity, High access rate, automated library system" (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - SEL 370 Dunn, Choi "Surface charge induction motor" inactive (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - SEL 371 Lehmann "Micro-measurement using blazed grating" (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - SEL 372 Kincheloe "Multiplex display system with delay addressing" (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - SEL 373 Kincheloe "Los cost high-speed electrically-controlled printing technique" inactive (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - SEL 374 S. J. Kline "Active turbofan wingtip vortex control" (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - SEL 375 S. J. Kline "Counter cross-flow vortex control" (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - SEL 376 M. L. Wright "Phased-array pattern generator system" (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - SEL 377 M. L. Wright "Phased-array providing continuous all-angle reception" (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - SEL 378 Goodman, Rhodes "Method for three-dimensional imaging with incoherent light" abandoned (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - SEL 379 Williams "Testing technique for L.-S. integrated sequential logic" abandoned (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - SEL 380 Walling "Liquid-gas phase change tactile transducer" (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - SEL 381 Nordstrom, Meindl "Field-effect modified bipolar transistor" (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - SEL 382 Musch "Open air infant incubator" (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - SEL 383 Samoun, Wise "Technique for etching thin diaphragms in silicon" (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - SEL 384 Wright "Phased array antenna driver" (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - SEL 385 Wright "high speed analog to digital converter" (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - SEL 386 Wright "High power high frequency amplifier" (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - SEL 387 Wright "Device for changing time behavior of signals" (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - SEL 388 Wright "Rapid wide-band sampling device" (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - SEL 389 Waldron, Newcom "Syneuristor" (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - SEL 390 Marshall, Peterson "Radar acoustic sounding system" (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - SEL 391 Cumming "Method for generating a notched spectrum" (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - SEL 392 Sweeney "Sweep-frequency feedline matching technique" (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - SEL 393 Taggart "Low cost antenna" inactive (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - SEL 394 Sword "Miniature intermittent contact switch" (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - SEL 395 Bandy "Silicon junction field-effect photodetector with large linear output" (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - SEL 396 Jindal "Purification of liquids by thin film freezing" (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - SEL 397 Moffat "Transpiration radiometer" (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - SEL 398 Castillo, Kruger "Recovery of high-viscosity petroleum by steam from geothermal heat" (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - SEL 399 Huseby, Whalen, Sherby "Magnesium-Boron particulate composites" (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Records, Accession ARCH-1993-130
  Accession 1993-130 contains chron files consisting of copies of award notices and outgoing letters and memoranda, 1983-1988.
  - Chron files containing copies of award notices and outgoing letters and memoranda, 11/1/83 - 4/30/84 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chron files containing copies of award notices and outgoing letters and memoranda, 5/1/84 - 10/15/84 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chron files containing copies of award notices and outgoing letters and memoranda, 10/16/84 - 3/31/85 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chron files containing copies of award notices and outgoing letters and memoranda, 4/1/85 - 9/15/85 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chron files containing copies of award notices and outgoing letters and memoranda, 9/16/85 - 3/15/86 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Chron files containing copies of award notices and outgoing letters and memoranda, 3/16/86 - 8/31/86 (Box 1, Folder 6)